think I got it with R$1
and today I'm in here
I'm realizing 1 crazy dream
caraca hand
thank you my friend
how are you doing
ok João Valeu
today i am going to put charlie brown inside the village
now i need to find a homie over there at the gate
and fall in
bro before the game starts
pleasure
thanks saw bro
and
there
ah tamo together Cara
thanks for the whole village
caraca hand
what if I leave some brownie in every little bar
for you took a while
I'm going to even lie that I have several for now
and then everything is fine
mind does not give
OR is everything ok
I'm filling up the Cara bars now
has gate
bar
Charlie Brown and will be in the game
Santos and Fluminense now
I separated 1 quota of brownie to leave in bars
and then another EU do brand activation
connects
can't just sell
has to be more strategic
is on
deliver the brownie to the right person brother
puts yourself in the hand of a famous guy
what happens
this positions the brand
caraca hand
the red bro or brownie there
Projection
are here
oh right there
Projection
we created Charlie Brown and Junior
I will play there
that's where the tape is,
if not me,
who will be happy
tamo together
that's it brother
sometimes we have to be more expensive
to be able to make the stops
meet a guy
meet another guy
I got here
brother with real tasting can
I just left my Charlie Brown in Projota's hand
everything cool to the brand
buy yes
don't shoot there dude
I just went outside
Santos goal
thanks saw Gabriel
we are with brother